How tall are you?
你有多高？
Do you tower over your friends and family – or are they people you literally have to look up to?
你是比亲朋好友都高出一大截，还是需要抬头仰望他们？
Obviously, we’re not all the same, and size doesn’t really matter.
显然，人与人的身高各不相同，而身高其实并不重要。
But did you know that there’s a possibility that we’re all getting taller?
但你知道吗？人类的身高或许正在普遍增长。
Of course, our height is out of our control – it’s a biological fact, influenced partly by genetics.
当然，身高是我们无法控制的——这是一个生物学事实，部分受基因影响。
The idea that being taller gives you more power and authority might be a tall story, but according to David Robson, writing for BBC Future, “on the basis of first impressions alone, taller people may have the edge.”
认为个子高就拥有更多权力和权威的说法可能有些夸大其词，但为BBC未来频道撰稿的大卫·罗布森表示：“单从第一印象来看，个子高的人或许更占优势。”
He adds that despite some slight risks to your health, various studies have found that the greater your height, the higher you score on measures of happiness and enjoyment of life.
他还补充道，尽管身高较高会带来一些轻微的健康风险，但多项研究发现，身高越高的人，在幸福感和生活满意度的测评中得分往往越高。
If this makes you want to become loftier, it’s good to know that all of us are taller than we were 150 years ago – by as much as ten centimetres.
如果这让你也想长高一些，那有个消息可以告诉你：如今人类的身高比150年前高出了足足10厘米。
Scientists have known for a long time that humans with good diets and reliable access to food tend to grow taller and mature more quickly.
科学家早已发现，饮食良好且食物供应稳定的人群，往往身高更高、发育得更快。
Adult height in some countries has rocketed as they transformed into a developed society.
随着一些国家发展成为发达国家，这些国家人群的成年身高也出现了急剧增长。
In a recent study, scientists have discovered a brain receptor, called MC3R, linked to our growing process.
在最近的一项研究中，科学家发现了一种名为MC3R的大脑受体，它与人类的生长发育过程密切相关。
It’s thought to be the crucial link between food and sex development and growth.
研究人员认为，这种受体是连接食物摄入、性发育与身体生长的关键纽带。
Professor Sir Stephen O’Rahilly from Cambridge University told the BBC: “It tells the body we’re great here, we’ve got lots of food, so grow quickly, have puberty soon and make lots of babies.”
剑桥大学的斯蒂芬·奥雷利爵士教授在接受BBC采访时表示：“这种受体向身体传递信号：我们的生存环境很优越，食物充足，所以要快速生长、尽早进入青春期，并且繁育更多后代。”
This discovery could lead to drugs to improve muscle mass and treat delayed growth, UK researchers say.
英国研究人员称，这一发现有望促成新型药物的研发，用以增加肌肉量和治疗发育迟缓问题。
For those aspiring to be taller, we need to look at the Dutch, who stand head and shoulders above the rest of us as the tallest people in the world.
对于那些渴望长的更高的人来说，可以看看荷兰人——他们的身高远超其他国家的人群，是世界上最高的群体。
But there is a ceiling for height, and it’s reached when people achieve their genetic potential.
但身高增长存在一个上限，当人们的身高达到自身基因潜力的极限时，就不会再继续长高了。
But, of course lanky people have to stoop through doorways and struggle to fit in cars and can have joint and cardiovascular problems, so maybe we should be careful for what we wish for.
当然，身材瘦高的人需要弯腰才能穿过房门，坐进车里也很费劲，还可能出现关节和心血管方面的问题，所以或许我们对自己的愿望还是谨慎一些为好。